const rules = document.getElementById ('front-page-outer');
const chapters = document.getElementById ('chapter-outer');
const gameboard = document.getElementById ('question-container');
const question = document.getElementById ('question');
const answers = Array.from(document.getElementsByClassName ('answer-text'));
const chapter_one_questions = [ 
    {
        question: "Which heir the throne of Gondor cut off Sauron's finger and claimed the one ring for themselves?",
        option1: "Isildur",
        option2: "Denathor",
        option3: "Aragon",
        option4: "Éomer",
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What birthday was Bilbo Baggins celebraing the night he disapears?",
        option1: "115th Birthday",
        option2: "111th Birthday",
        option3: "112th Birthday",
        option4: "113th Birthday",
        correct: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "After Merry and Pippin light the large firework from Gandalf's stock, which creature appears when it explodes?",
        option1: "An Eagle",
        option2: "An Ent",
        option3: "A Dragon",
        option4: "A Nazgul",
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What two words does the creature Gollum shout when tortured about the Ring?",
        option1: "Bilbo, Baggins",
        option2: "Shire, Baggins",
        option3: "The, Shire",
        option4: "Ring, Baggins",
        correct: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the Inn found at Bree that the four Hobbits were to meet Gandalf at?",
        option1: "The Green Dragon",
        option2: "The Rusty Spoon",
        option3: "The Horse and Cart",
        option4: "The Prancing Pony",
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which weapon did the Wraith attack Froddo with at Weathertop?",
        option1: "An Elvish Knife",
        option2: "A Dwarfish Axe",
        option3: "A Morgul Blade",
        option4: "An Orc Sword",
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "After Lord Elrond declares that the one Ring should be destroyed, which character attempts to destory it?",
        option1: "Legolas",
        option2: "Froddo",
        option3: "Gimli",
        option4: "Boromir",
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Character famously says the line 'One does not simply walk into Mordor'?",
        option1: "Legolas",
        option2: "Elrond",
        option3: "Gimli",
        option4: "Boromir",
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of the Lord of Moria, whose coffin the Fellowship come across in the mines?",
        option1: "Gloin",
        option2: "Balin",
        option3: "Durin",
        option4: "Dáin",
        correct: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Hobbit knocks debris down the well in Moria to alert the Orcs to the Fellowships presence?",
        option1: "Sam",
        option2: "Froddo",
        option3: "Merrin",
        option4: "Pippin",
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the creature known as 'Durin's Bane' found in the mines?",
        option1: "Balrog",
        option2: "Smaug",
        option3: "Shelob",
        option4: "Mumakil",
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What gift does the Lady Galadriel give to Froddo before the Fellowship leave LothLorien?",
        option1: "The Light of Eärendil",
        option2: "The Sting",
        option3: "Mithril",
        option4: "A Cloak",
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which character attempts to steal the ring from Froddo?",
        option1: "Legolas",
        option2: "Sam",
        option3: "Boromir",
        option4: "Aragon",
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Uruk-Hai kills Boromir?",
        option1: "Azog",
        option2: "Gothmog",
        option3: "Uglúk",
        option4: "Lurtz",
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which two Hobbits are taken by the Uruk-Hai?",
        option1: "Merry and Sam",
        option2: "Pippin and Sam",
        option3: "Merry and Pippin",
        option4: "Sam and Froddo",
        correct: 3,
    }
];